Guide to the Rick Lazio Papers, 1981–2005
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Congressional Papers
  - Subject File
    - Senior Citizen Issues, Misc., (Newsletters, Press Clippings Featuring Rick Lazio), 1997-1998 (Box 103)
    - Speech Development Notes, (Notes On Raising Quality of Speech Preservation…Includes Talking Points On Israel), Oct 1997 (Box 103)
    - Tax Reform Issues, (Talking Points, Background Material), Oct 1997 (Box 103)
    - Tibet, Congressman Frank Wolf Visit, (Report, Correspondence), Aug-Sep 1997 (Box 103)
    - United Nations Development Program, (Correspondence), Jun 1997 (Box 103)
    - Volunteerism, (Press Clippings, Packet From President’s Summit For America’s Future), Jan-Apr 1997 (Box 103)
    - Voting Records, Rick Lazio/Susan Molinari, Jan-Jul 1997 (Box 103)
    - American Chiropractic Association, (Correspondence), Jan-May 1998 (Box 103)
    - Breast Cancer, (Media Hits Jul 1998, Lazio Chronology RE: Breast Cancer (Box 103)
    - Cancer, Children, (Proposal To Rick Lazio With RL’s Notes, Talking Points, Childhood Cancer Briefing), May-Nov 1998 (Box 103)
    - Central Banks In Emerging Markets, (Correspondence, Memoranda, Research Material), 1998; (2 folders) (Box 103)
    - Clinical Trials Database, (Background Material, Briefing Report), Aug 1998 (Box 103)
    - Cold War – CNN Reportage, (Correspondence), Mar 1996-Oct 1998 (Box 103)
    - Dowling College Global Learning Center, (Letters of Support For Model School Proposal), Jun-Aug 1998 (Box 103)
    - Dowling College Global Learning Center, (Funding Request Correspondence), Aug-Oct 1998; (2 folders) (Box 103)
    - Education – Bi-Lingual Comprehensive Grant, (Correspondence), Jun 1998 (Box 103)
    - Education – Dowling Global Learning Center, (Correspondence, Notes, Proposals), May 1998 (Box 103)
    - Education Legislation Co-Sponsorship, (After School Children’s Education Act Correspondence), Sep 1998 (Box 103)
    - Education – Stony Brook State University of N.Y., (Correspondence), Feb 1997-Feb 1998 (Box 103)
    - Electronic Data Gathering, Analysis, Retrieval (Edgar), (Correspondence, Background Material, Notes), 1998 (Box 104)
    - Federal Budget and The States, FY 1997 Report, (Includes Cover Letter From Sen. Patrick Moynihan, 10/15/1998) (Box 104)
    - Fire Island, (Lazio Accomplishments, News Interview Talking Points…8/10/1998, Press Clippings) (Box 104)
    - Grenada – Castro Visit, (Memoranda), Jan-Feb 1998 (Box 104)
    - Health Care Issues, (Lazio Press Releases, Op-Ed Text, Misc. Accomplishments), Mar 1998-Aug 1999 (Box 104)
    - Hemophilia Treatment Centers, (Correspondence, Background Material, Notes), 1998; (2 folders) (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, (Draft of Letter To Constituents, Minority Dissenting Views, Congressional Statements), 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, (Draft Statements By Rick Lazio…Written on Air Force One…Regarding Impeachment of Pres. Bill Clinton…Includes Handwritten Draft With Revisions), 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, (Letters To R. Lazio Supporting/Opposing Impeachment of Pres. Bill Clinton…Includes Letter Opposing Impeachment From Laurence Rockefeller, 12/10/1998) (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, (Rick Lazio Floor Statement On Impeachment of Pres. Bill Clinton, Drafts, Notes, Press Clippings), Dec 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, Committee On The Judiciary Report, Dec 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, House Resolution 611, (Report of the Committee On The Judiciary Impeachment of Pres. Bill Clinton), 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, Lazio Floor Statement, (House Resolution Language For Impeachment of Pres. Bill Clinton), 18 Dec 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, Lazio Press Release, Correspondence, Summary of Arguments, White House Text, (Clinton Address At White House Prayer Meeting), Aug-Dec 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, Lazio Statements, (Press Clippings, Texas Review of Law and Politics…Clinton and Gore Scandals and Impeachment), 1998 (Box 104)
    - Impeachment, Op-Ed Draft By R. Lazio, (Discussion Points, Press Clippings), Dec 1998 (Box 105)
    - Impeachment, Press Clippings, Talking Points, Nov-Dec 1998 (Box 105)
    - Impeachment, Report – Submission By Counsel For Pres. Clinton To the Committee on the Judiciary…, Dec 1998; (2 folders) (Box 105)
    - Iraq, (Memoranda/Update, Congressional Research Memo), Feb 1998 (Box 105)
    - Iraq, Saddam Hussein, (Essay By Rick Lazio), 1998 (Box 105)
    - Israel, Middle East – Lazio Record On Israel, Various Texts Written By R. Lazio, 1998 (Box 105)
    - Kosovo, (Testimonies From Hearing, Commission on Security and Cooperation In Europe…Includes Letter From Pres. Bill Clinton), 28 Dec 1998 (Box 105)
    - Leibell, Vinnie – Senator NY State, (Correspondence, Background Information), Dec 1998 (Box 105)
    - Letter To Editor, ‘Arts In America’, New York Times, (Includes Lazio Statement On Weapons of Mass Destruction), 20 Feb 1998 (Box 105)
    - Levy, Senator Norman J., (Tribute and Floor Statement By R. Lazio, Obituary, Copy of Letter From R. Lazio To Levy’s Son), Jan-Mar 1998 (Box 105)
    - Lyrics For Sing-alongs, Research Paper By Lazio Staffer, Victory Speech Text By R. Lazio, 1998 (Box 105)
    - Mafia, Disney Film, (R. Lazio Press Release, Report – Portrayal of Italian-American Characters In Prime Time T.V.), Jul 1998 (Box 105)
    - Misc. Awards Honoring Rick Lazio, (Correspondence), Aug-Oct 1998 (Box 105)
    - MIA/POW/China, (Correspondence To/From Clinton, Bill), Jun 1998 (Box 105)
    - NY Rural Letter Carriers Association, (Notes, Descriptions of H.R. 3126), 1998 (Box 105)
    - NEA – Issue Outline, (Correspondence, Biographical Portfolio of Pasquale J. Curcio), May-Nov 1998 (Box 105)
    - N.E.A. Lazio Chronology Of Events, Defending The N.E.A., Jan 1997-Jun 1998 (Box 105)
    - National Senior Service Corps, (Background Materials), 1998 (Box 105)
    - National Senior Service Corps, (Draft Letter From R. Lazio, Correspondence, Notes, Foster Grandparent Correspondence), Jan 1997-Apr 1998 (Box 105)
    - New York City Housing Authority Journal, (Interview Text, Correspondence), Aug 1997-Jul 1998 (Box 105)
    - Northrop-Grumman/Lockheed Martin Merger, (Press Release, Correspondence), Nov 1997-Mar 1998 (Box 105)
    - Op-Ed, Chemical/Biological Weapons, (Draft of Text, Letters To Editors ("The Growing Threat of Biological Attack", Feb-May 1998), (2 folders) (Box 105)
    - Op-Ed, Economic Impact of NYC’s Housing Investment, (Correspondence, Research Material), 1998 (Box 106)
    - Pataki, George – 1998 Budget Proposal, (Includes Email Notes From 12/1998 Mtg. With Governor (Box 106)
    - Radio Station – WLUX, Long Island, (Correspondence, Background Material), Oct 1998-Aug 1999; (2 folders) (Box 106)
    - Report, Wirthlin Worldwide, (Pulse Line Speech Assessment), 22 Jun 1998 (Box 106)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Medal of Honor, (Testimony Text, Issue Discussion, Background Material For Medal of Honor Testimony, Includes T. Roosevelt Association Journal With Lazio Article – Fall 1997), 1998; (3 folders) (Box 106)
    - Transurethral Microwave Thermotherapy, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jan-May 1998 (Box 106)
    - Water Resources Development Act, (Correspondence and Background Material), Mar 1998 (Box 106)
    - Amway Corp., (Correspondence), Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 106)
    - Anvirzel/Cancer Treatment, (Correspondence), Jun-Jul 1999 (Box 106)
    - Budget – FY 2000, (Congressional Budget Office Correspondence, Background Material), Jun-Oct 1999 (Box 106)
    - Budget For F.Y. 2000, Clinton Administration, (Summary and Critique By House Com. On The Budget Majority Caucus), Feb 1999 (Box 106)
    - Central Islip Courthouse, Survey on Courthouse Name, (Correspondence, Survey Responses), Apr-Dec 1999 (Box 107)
    - Cold War Certificate, (Correspondence, Press Clippings, Res. 180 – Cold War Commencement), Mar 1996-Jan 1999 (Box 107)
    - Cold War Recognition Certificate Program, (Press Releases, Correspondence, Notes), Feb-Sep 1999; (2 folders) (Box 107)
    - Congressional Research Service Reports, (RE: Congressional Salaries, Minimum Wage), Mar 1990-Oct 1999 (Box 107)
    - Daily Schedule For Rick Lazio, Jan-Dec 1999 (Box 107)
    - Death Tax, A Citizen’s Guide To The Death Tax, 1999 (Box 107)
    - Debt Reduction, (Research, Background Material, Notes), Jun-Jul 1999 (Box 107)
    - Education Issues, Misc., (General Background Materials, Correspondence and Press Clippings), Feb 1997-May 1999 (Box 107)
    - Educational Training, Empowering Educators, (Background Information, Press Clippings, Correspondence), 1999 (Box 107)
    - Fire Island Coastal Protection, (Briefing Book, Talking Points, Correspondence, Press Release, Background Material), 1999 (Box 107)
    - Fire Island, (Fact Sheet For Senators Moynihan, Schumer, Reps. Forbes and Lazio, Correspondence), Apr-Dec 1999 (Box 107)
    - GSE Dynamics Federal Contract, (Correspondence), May 1996-Jan 1997 (Box 107)
    - Gun Control, (Correspondence), Jun-Sep 1999 (Box 107)
    - Health Care Financing Administration, Fraud Management/Abuse, (Questionnaire Completed By R. Lazio, Correspondence), Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 108)
    - Information Technology Industry Council, (Congressional Voting Record), 1999 (Box 108)
    - Libertarian Party of New York, (Correspondence, Independent Party Voting Record), Feb 1999 (Box 108)
    - Medicare and Mental Health, (Correspondence, Background Information), Jan-Oct 1999 (Box 108)
    - Memoranda Regarding N.Y. State Sports Trivia, Jun 1999 (Box 108)
    - OB-GYN – The American College of OB-GYN, (Correspondence, Background Material), 1999 (Box 108)
    - Op-Ed Natural Disasters, (Drafts of Text, Correspondence, Hearing Statement), 1999 (Box 108)
    - Op-Ed, Postal Modernization Act of 1999, (Drafts, Correspondence, Notes), Jan 1999 (Box 108)
    - Pirro, Jeannine, Westchester Co. D.A., (Press Clipping, Email), Jan-Feb 1999 (Box 108)
    - Review of Clinton Budget For F.Y., 1999 (Box 108)
    - Salaries of Members of Congress, (Summary of Current Procedures), 1999 (Box 108)
    - Tax Cuts For New York, (Speech Draft, Background Material), Jun 1999 (Box 108)
    - Teacher Mentor Program, (Correspondence, Background Material), Feb-Mar 1999; (2 folders) (Box 108)
    - Veterans Health Care Funding, (Colloquy Text), 1999 (Box 108)
    - Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Lexis/Nexis Search Request), Oct-Nov 1999 (Box 108)
    - Zip Code Change, Village of Islandia, Dec 1999 (Box 108)
    - Computers and Email - Miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box 162)
    - Clemency Petition For Former Long Island President, Marie La Pinta, Nov 2000 (Box 108)
    - Crime Bill, (Correspondence, Press Clippings), Aug 1994-Jun 2000 (Box 108)
    - Daily Schedule for Rick Lazio, Jan-Dec 2000 (Box 108)
    - Education – Next Generation Technology, (Correspondence, Bill Language), 2000 (Box 109)
    - Fire Island Interim Project, (Press Statement, Correspondence, Press Points, Background Information), May 1997-Jan 2000 (Box 109)
    - Holocaust Assets, (Floor Statement By R. Lazio, Correspondence), Jun 1999-Feb 2000 (Box 109)
    - League of Conservation Voters, (Questionnaires Sent To R. Lazio, Correspondence To/From R. Lazio, Scorecards…Environmental…For R. Lazio), Jun 2000; (2 folders) (Box 109)
    - Medicare Payment Advisory Commission, (Nominations, Background Information), Mar 2000 (Box 109)
    - Minimum Wage, (Background Material, Press Releases, Talking Points), Mar-Aug 2000 (Box 109)
    - Palestinian State, (Middle East Peace Process Act Talking Points), Jul 2000 (Box 109)
    - Staff Reference File, (David Horne, Andrew Elrich), 2000 (Box 109)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Medal of Honor, (Press Releases and Background Material), Oct 1997-Jan 2000 (Box 109)
    - Budget Review Report, Clinton Admin., 2001 (Box 109)
    - Theodore Roosevelt, Thank You Card From Vernon School Third Graders For Success RE: Roosevelt Medal of Honor, (Includes Press Clippings), 2001 (Box 109)
    - Form Letters on Various Issues, original Word Perfect files, 1996-2000; (4 floppy disks) (Box 162)
    - Form Letters on Various Issues, MS Word files, 1996-2000; (1 cd) (Box 162)
    - Phone Call Log, Jan-Dec 1997 (Box 162)
    - Phone Call Log, Jan-Dec 1998; (2 folders) (Box 162)
    - Phone Call Log, Jan-Dec 1999; (3 folders) (Box 162)
    - Phone Call Log, Jan-Dec 2000; (2 folders) (Box 162)
    - Unlabeled SyQuest 44 MB Removable Disk Cartridge from LUM and Associates Advertising and Graphic Design, undated (Box 162)
  - Travel
    - Jerusalem/Jewish Community Relations Council, (Itinerary, Correspondence, U.J.A. Program With Hand-Written Notes, Background Material), Dec 1993 (Box 110)
    - Sallsbury State University Republican Conference, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jan 1994 (Box 110)
    - California, Federal Credit Union, (Lazio Talking Points, Itinerary), Oct 1995 (Box 110)
    - Chicago, Subcommittee Hearing, Housing and Community Opportunity, (Correspondence, Lazio Statement, Background Material), Sep-Oct 1995 (Box 110)
    - Ireland, Ripon Educational Fund/Transatlantic Conference, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Aug 1995 (Box 110)
    - Arkansas, Housing Forum, (Itinerary, Background Material), Aug 1996 (Box 110)
    - California, National Republican Congressional Committee, (Correspondence, Itinerary), Feb 1996 (Box 110)
    - Florida, NY State Food Merchants Association, (Speech, Correspondence), Mar 1996 (Box 110)
    - New Orleans, Housing Authority of New Orleans, (Itinerary, Background Material), Jul 1996 (Box 110)
    - Philadelphia, Field Hearing, (Correspondence, Itinerary), 1996 (Box 110)
    - Rome, Transatlantic Conference, (Itinerary, Correspondence, Participants List), Oct-Nov 1996; (2 folders) (Box 110)
    - San Diego, Republican National Convention, (Event Calendar, Correspondence, Guidelines, Convention Goals/Message, Convention Guidelines, General Info), Aug 1996; (3 folders) (Box 110)
    - Ft. Lauderdale, FLA – American Israel Public Affairs Committee, (Correspondence, Background Material), 1997 (Box 110)
    - Hershey, PA – Bi-Partisan Congressional Retreat, (Correspondence, Briefing Book With Handwritten Notes by R. Lazio), Mar 1997 (Box 111)
    - New York City – Freedom Alliance, Oct 1997 (Box 111)
    - Orlando, FL – Tax Credit Conference For Affordable Housing Developers, (Itinerary, Correspondence, Background Material), Jan 1997 (Box 111)
    - Palm Beach, FLA – A.G.E.S. Group, (Itinerary, Correspondence, Background Material), Mar 1997 (Box 111)
    - Prague/Czech Republic, (1997 Transatlantic Conference, Travel Agendas, Press Release, Background Material), 8-16 Aug 1997; (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Puerto Rico, (Schedule, Bios of Attendees, Press Clippings), Jun 1997; (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Williamsburg, VA – Congressional Institute, (Budget Presentation Print-Out, Correspondence, Background Material), Feb 1997, 1998, 1999 (Box 111)
    - Chicago, IL – National Kidney Cancer Association, (Speech Text, Itinerary, Correspondence), 1998 (Box 111)
    - Israel – Presidential Trip To The Middle East, (Itinerary (Program Book With Lazio Notes) Letter From Pres. Clinton (1/25/1999), Correspondence), Dec 1998 (Box 111)
    - Israel – Presidential Trip To The Middle East, (Preparatory Material Provided For Trip…Fact Sheets, Briefings), 11-15 Dec 1998; (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Israel – Presidential Trip To The Middle East, (Press release, Speech of Yasser Arafat, Briefings, Reports Prepared For Trip), Dec 1998 (Box 112)
    - Israel – Presidential Trip To The Middle East, (General Information Package For Trip, Remarks by Pres. Clinton, Mrs. Clinton, Lazio Op-Ed Text, ‘Washington File’ News Clips From Trip), 12-15 Dec 1998 (Box 112)
    - Nantucket, MA, Aug 1998 (Box 112)
    - New York City – NYS Arts Council, Apr 1998 (Box 112)
    - Orlando, FLA – Developers Tax Credit Conference, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Jan 1998 (Box 112)
    - Palm Beach, FLA – Republican National Conference, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Jan 1999 (Box 112)
    - Palm Springs, CA – National Republican Congressional Committee, (Itinerary, Correspondence, Agenda/Program), Feb 1998 (Box 112)
    - Pinehurst, NC – National Republican Congressional Committee, (Agenda, R. Lazio Talking Points, Background Material), Jun 1998 (Box 112)
    - St. Thomas/U.S.V.I. – Television and Radio Political Action Committee, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Feb 1998 (Box 112)
    - Albania, Codel – Congressional Delegation Army, (Correspondence, Background Material), Apr-May 1999 (Box 112)
    - Belfast, Ireland – Habitat For Humanity, (Trip By Lazio Staffer, Jessica Lynch), Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 112)
    - Chatham, MA – Congressional Leadership Educational Seminar Invest to Compete Alliance, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jul 1999 (Box 112)
    - Hershey, PA – Bi-Partisan Retreat, (Correspondence, Background Material), Mar 1999 (Box 112)
    - Kosovo/Balkans, (Press Releases, Talking Points, Correspondence, Notes, Background Material, Press Clippings), Mar-Apr 1999; (3 folders) (Box 112)
    - Lake George, NY – NY State Broadcasters Association, (Talking Points Include Senate Campaign Issues), Jun 1999 (Box 113)
    - Lake George, NY – Republican Eagles Summer National Meeting, (Itinerary, Background Material), Aug 1999 (Box 113)
    - Mohonk Mountain House, NY – Consulting Engineers, NY State, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jun 1999 (Box 113)
    - N.Y. Upstate Swing/ GOP, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Apr 1999 (Box 113)
    - N.Y. Upstate Swing/Republican Committee, (Speech Draft, Notes, Correspondence), Feb 1999 (Box 113)
    - New York City – National Republican Congressional Committee, (Itineraries, Correspondence), Dec 1999 (Box 113)
    - Orlando, FLA – Developers Tax Credit Conference, (Itinerary, Correspondence, Background Material), Jan 1999 (Box 113)
    - Philadelphia, PA – National Republican Senatorial Committee, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jul 1999 (Box 113)
    - U.K./Germany – Codel Hastert, (Correspondence, Itinerary, Background Material), Sep 1999 (Box 113)
    - University of VA, Charlottesville, VA – National Homeownership Summit, (Itinerary, Correspondence), Nov 1999 (Box 113)
- Series III. Senate Campaign Papers
  - Campaign Files
    - Clinton, Hillary, (Campaign Flyers, Handbills), 2000 (Box 114)
    - Clinton, Hillary and Senate Race, (Email Correspondence/Clinton Criticisms) – CONFIDENTIAL, Aug-Oct 2000; (5 folders) (Box 114)
    - Donation Forms Supporting Lazio Campaign – CONFIDENTIAL, 2000 (Box 114)
    - Volunteer email - CONFIDENTIAL, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Correspondence
    - ‘Crank’ Letter File – CONFIDENTIAL, May-Nov 2000 (Box 114)
    - Letters of Support From Constituents For Senate Campaign, Aug-Sep 2000 (Box 114)
  - Press Coverage
    - Press Clippings RE: Positioning of R. Lazio For Senate, (Includes Email Request For Specific Press Clippings), Nov 1998-Feb 1999 (Box 114)
    - Press Clippings RE: Hillary Clinton, Jan 1999-Jun 1999 (Box 114)
    - Press Clippings RE: Hillary Clinton, Jun 1999-Dec 1999 (Box 114)
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint - re: Hillary Clinton), Aug 1995-Jul 1996 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), Jan 1999-Dec 1999 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), Jun 2000 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), Jul 2000 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), Aug 2000 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), Sep 2000 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), Oct-Nov 2000 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), undated (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, (newsprint – re: Hillary Clinton), undated (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Press Clippings, May-Jun 2000; (5 folders) (Box 114)
    - Press Releases RE: Lazio Senate Campaign, Aug-Oct 2000 (Box 116)
  - Speech File
    - Allegany County GOP Annual Luncheon, 18 Sep 1999 (Box 116)
    - Allegany County Republican Committee Luncheon, 18 Sep 1999 (Box 116)
    - Congressional Club Breakfast Reception, 17 Oct 1999 (Box 116)
    - Jamestown, NY Rally, 17 Sep 1999 (Box 116)
    - Montgomery County Steak Roast, 27 Jun 1999 (Box 116)
    - National Republican Senatorial Committee Meeting, 22 Jul 1999 (Box 116)
    - Republican Eagles Speech, 12 Jan 1999 (Box 116)
    - Senate Campaign Announcement Speech, undated (Box 116)
    - Stump Speeches, Speech Critique Memo, 1999 (Box 116)
    - U.S. – Israel, (Memoranda, Correspondence Material Used For Talking Points, Includes Letter RE: Jerusalem Embassy Act of 1995 From Pres. Clinton), 13 Jul 1999 (Box 116)
    - Wayne County, (Text For Videotape, Includes R. Lazio Notes), undated (Box 116)
    - Good Samaritan Hospice Children’s Services, (Hecksher State Park), undated (Box 116)
    - Senate Campaign Announcement, 26 Jul 1999, 21 May 2000 (Box 116)
    - Speeches, Jan-Jun 2000 (Box 117)
    - Speeches, (‘Larry King’ Transcript (1/17/2000)RE: Hillary Clinton and NT Racial Politics, Lazio Included In Panel), Jan-Apr 2000 (Box 117)
  - Subject File
    - Accomplishments…Legislative, Awards – Rick Lazio, (Correspondence RE: Gingrich and Moynihan Senate Seats), Nov 1998-2000 (Box 117)
    - Giuliani, Rudolf, (Press Clippings), Mar 1998-Feb 1999 (Box 117)
    - Hinchey, Maurice D., (Press Clippings…negative, Preliminary Vulnerability Assessment Report), Jan-Mar 1998 (Box 117)
    - Press Time Line, (Summary Regarding Polls, Hillary Clinton, Rudy Giuliani Press Clipping RE: Economy), 14 Apr 1994 (Box 117)
    - T.V. Interview Summaries, Practice Questions, (Addresses Rudy Giuliani and Hillary Clinton Issues), Mar-Apr 1994 (Box 117)
    - Accomplishments and Positions of Rick Lazio…Includes Report ‘Legislative Accomplishments In 106th Congress,’, 2000-2001 (Box 117)
    - Daily Schedules For Congressman Rick Lazio, (Includes Articles RE: Congressional Scheduling), Oct-Nov 2000; (6 folders) (Box 118)
    - Daily Schedules For Congressman Rick Lazio, (6 of 6), Nov 2000 (Box 118)
    - Schedules, Daily Schedules For Mrs. Pat Lazio, Jul-Nov 2000 (Box 118)
    - Fundraising Contacts, (Mailing Lists, Correspondence, Volunteer Information), 2000 (Box 118)
    - New York Freedom From Soft Money Pact (Press Releases, Form Letter), Sep 2000 (Box 118)
    - Volunteer Sign-In Sheets, 2000; (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Phone Call Lists, Correspondence, Mar-Jul 2000 (Box 162)
- Series IV. Press Coverage
  - Press Clippings
    - 6 Feb-8 Nov 1992 (Box 141)
    - Dec 1992-Dec 1993 (Box 119)
    - Op-Ed Articles and Misc. Columns By Rick Lazio, (Crime, Home Ownership, Israel, HUD, NAFTA…) (Box 141)
    - Jan-Dec 1994 (Box 119)
    - Jan-Jun 1995 (Box 119)
    - Jun-Dec 1995 (Box 119)
    - Jan-May 1996 (Box 119)
    - May-Aug 1996 (Box 119)
    - Aug-Dec 1996 (Box 119)
    - Jan-Jun 1997 (Box 120)
    - Jun-Sep 1997 (Box 120)
    - Sep-Dec 1997 (Box 120)
    - Jan-Feb 1998 (Box 120)
    - Mar-May 1998 (Box 120)
    - Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 120)
    - Jul-Aug 1998 (Box 121)
    - Sep-Dec 1998 (Box 121)
    - Jan 1999 (Box 121)
    - Feb 1999, (4 folders) (Boxes 121, 122)
    - Mar 1999, (4 folders) (Box 122)
    - Apr 1999, (4 folders) (Boxes 122,123)
    - May 1999, (3 folders) (Box 123)
    - Jun 1999, (4 folders) (Boxes 123, 124)
    - Jul 1999, (4 folders) (Box 124)
    - Aug 1999, (3 folders) (Box 125)
    - Sep 1999, (4 folders) (Box 125)
    - Oct 1999, (4 folders) (Box 126)
    - Nov 1999, (4 folders) (Box 126)
    - Dec 1999, (3 folders) (Box 127)
    - Jan 2000, (3 folders) (Box 127)
    - Feb-Apr 2000 (Box 127)
    - 7 Feb 2000 (Box 127)
    - 8-11 Feb 2000 (Box 127)
    - 14-16 Feb 2000 (Box 128)
    - 17-22 Feb 2000 (Box 128)
    - 23-24 Feb 2000 (Box 128)
    - 25-29 Feb 2000 (Box 128)
    - 1-2 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 6-7 Mar 2000 (Box 128)